<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BADSHA HANDICAPPER TIPS</string>
    <string name="name">Badsha Professional Handicapper\n Indian Race Tips</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading....</string>
    <string name="contact_us_details">About Us \n


Badsha Race Tips \n

Home \n
Center \n
Archives \n
Race Card \n
Track Work \n
Scale Rating \n
Speed Rating \n
Bend Position Rating \n
Media Choices \n
Best Tips \n
BADSHA HANDICAPPER CHOICES \n
Results \n
Query/Feed back \n
Privacy Policy \n
Terms and Conditions \n
Guidelines \n


<b>About Us</b>\n

BADSHA PROFESSIONAL HANDICAPPER – Badsha has been one of the most trusted names in Horse Racing and tipping for over a decade. He has a simple rule. The punter must go home with more than he entered the betting ring. With this philosophy, he has managed to make thousands of punters richer with his accurate race analysis and handicapping. He now comes out with the mobile app to make the same advice available to the national audience. The application is managed by Badsha and his committed and highly professional team who uses the best scientific tools to come out with the best choice of horse to bet on for win, place, SHP, THP and jackpot. The complete process is overseen and managed by Badsha personally and the Speed Rating Algorithm is managed by Amitabh Dutta. The app has been developed by Tara Web Studio in collaboration with Hamiters, Hyderabad under the strict supervision of Badsha. \n
All information and data provided herein this mobile App BADSHA PROFESSIONAL HANDICAPPER is for reference purpose only. BADSHA HANDICAPPER make no representation or warranty of any kind regarding data on this Mobile App Services nor the data and information published or referred to on each pages associated with this App. Also note videos are the properties of the respective clubs. BADSHA only gives a link to the respective race club’s websites or to the one which are available in public domain. Videos will play only if they are in compatible form. BADSHA Tips subscription doesn’t includes Videos. The Videos and its availability is not guaranteed by us. \n

CONTACT: \n
EMAIL: support@papadsanjay5555.com \n
WHAT DO YOU GET WITH THE DIAMOND PLAN \n

1) RACE CARD: Day card details with last run details and the video of the last run if available. \n

2) TRACKWORK: Track work of the horse after his last run till the date of the race. \n

3) BADSHA CHOICE: Race wise choice of BADSHA including WIN, SHP, THP.TANALA, JACKPOT PICKS. \n

4) BEST BETS: This page will offer Days Best, Good Double, Good Place, Lay bet, Treble and Jackpot. \n

5) MEDIA TIPS: The tips from all major media outlets covering racing including the major blog sites. \n

6) SPEED RATING: The selection here are based on a proprietary algorithm created by Badsha Professional Handicapper team and Mr. Amitabh Dutta. \n

7) SCALE RATING \n
The difference between the top weight horse and the bottom weight horse is called the scale and has a huge significance on how to read the race card. For instance, if the scale of the race is very wide with the top weight at 62 kgs and bottom weight at 45 kgs, the horses carrying the flyweight on their backs have a higher chance of winning even if they are not as prodigious as the top weight horses. If the scale is small, then the weight differential is lesser and only applies to the line through which the horses have run together in the past. In short, scale analysis helps you decipher the effect of the weight the horse is carrying. We will help you take informed decision with regards to the chances that a horse has based on the weight it s carrying. \n

8) SPEED RATING \n
Most punters are confused on how to compare two horses which have run at different weights under different conditions with different jockeys because all these factors affect the final position of the horse. Thus a horse carrying 60 kgs will travel slower than a horse traveling at 55 kgs. It’s easier to run on hard ground than soft ground. So how can you compare two horses? With our proprietary algorithm, we put values for all these variables, factoring in weight, jockeys and trainers abilities, and condition of the ground, wind speed, length of the straight, and distance from the rails etc. to arrive at a figure that you can use to easily compare two horses. This figure can help you select between all the possible horses and make an efficient decision on your betting. \n

9) BEND POSITION ANALYSIS \n
The bend position is a major contributor to the ability of the horse in winning a race. When we analyse the chances of a horse winning a race, we have to look at the aerodynamics of horse racing. Horses which hit the bend early find it easier to navigate the turn unless a backmarker can get an opening through the bunch ahead. On the other hand, in order to hit the bend early, the horse has to expend more energy making it vulnerable in the straight if it cannot get the necessary wind to overhaul the final stages. Therefore most long distance races, the clever jockey will position his horse in the pace so that it does not have to face the air resistance when turning 3 or 4 deep. We will help you understand when the horse is probable to hit the bend and how does that affect its chances in the race. \n

10) RESULT: The result will be displayed only after being officially announced by the club’s website or announced at race course board. \n







Guidelines \n

WIN: The Horse should finish FIRST. \n

SECOND HORSE POOL (SHP): The Horse should finish SECOND. \n

THIRD HORSE POOL (THP): The Horse should finish THIRD. \n

PLACE: The Horse should finish in FIRST TWO. (If 7 runner) \n

The Horse should finish in FIRST THREE. (If above 7 runner) \n

TANALA: The Horse should finish 1-2-3 or 2-3-1 or 3-2-1. (Any order from 1 to 3) \n

JACKPOT: Select WINNER Horse of nominated 5 Races by club. \n
We will provide you with the best selections for the Jackpot ticket and the price of the same. \n</string>


    <string name="privacy_policy"><u>Badsha Professional Handicapaper Tips</u>\n\n
Home\n
Center\n
Archives\n
Race Card\n
Track Work\n
Scale Rating\n
Speed Rating\n
Bend Position Rating \n
Media Choice\n
Best Tips\n
BADSHA HANDICAPPER CHOICES\n
Results\n
Query/Feedback\n
Privacy Policy\n
Terms and Conditions\n
Guidlines\n
Expires On\n
Version 4.0\n\n
TERMS OF SERVICE\n

The terms and conditions for all End users of the BADSHA PROFESSIONAL HANDICAPPER, for the services are available on BADSHA HANDICAPPER Mobile app.\nThe Mobile App is owned and operated by (“BADSHA HANDICAPPER”).\nThe App is offered subject to your acceptance without modification of all of the terms and conditions contained herein and all other operating rules, policies (including, without limitation, BADSHA HANDICAPPER’s Privacy Policy) and procedures that may be published from time to time on this App by BADSHA HANDICAPPER as agreed by consent.\nBy using any part of the App, you agree to become bound by the terms and conditions of this agreement.\nIf you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the App or use any services.\nThe App can only be used by the person aged 18 and above.\n\n

• BADSHA HANDICAPPER have fully complied with any third-party licenses relating to the Content, and have done all things necessary to successfully pass through to end users any required terms;\n
• The Content does not contain or install any viruses, worms, malware, Trojan horses or other harmful or destructive content;\n
• The Content is not spam, is not machine- or randomly-generated, and does not contain unethical or unwanted commercial content designed to drive traffic to third party sites or boost the search engine rankings of third party sites, or to further unlawful acts such as phishing or mislead recipients as to the source of the material such as spoofing.\n
• The Content is not pornographic, does not contain threats or incite violence towards individuals or entities, and does not violate the privacy or publicity rights of any third party;\n
• The App is not getting advertised via unwanted electronic messages such as spam links on newsgroups, email lists, other blogs and web sites, and similar unsolicited promotional methods.\n
• The App is not named in a manner that misleads our readers into thinking that we are another person or company. For example, our site URL or name is not the name of a person other than our self or company other than our own;\n
We have, in the case of Content that includes computer code, accurately categorized and/or described the type, nature, uses and effects of the materials, whereer requested to do so by Badsha Handicapper  or otherwise.\nBy submitting Content to Badsha Handicapper for inclusion on your Website, you grant Badsha Handicapper a world-wide, royalty-free, and non-exclusive license to reproduce, modify, adapt and publish the Content solely for the purpose of displaying, distributing and promoting your site.\nIf you delete Content, Badsha Handicapper will use reasonable efforts to remove it from the Website, but you acknowledge that caching or references to the Content may not be made immediately unavailable.\nWithout limiting any of those representations or warranties, Badsha Handicapper has the right though not the obligation to, in Badsha Handicapper’s sole discretion (1) refuse or remove any content that, in Badsha Handicapper’s reasonable opinion, violates any Badsha Handicapper policy or is in any way harmful or objectionable, or (2) terminate or deny access to and use of the Website to any individual or entity for any reason, in Badsha Handicapper’s sole discretion. Badsha Handicapper will have no obligation to provide a refund of any amounts previously paid.\n\n


1. Subscription Fees and Support\nBy signing up for a Services account you agree to pay the applicable setup fees and recurring fees. Applicable fees will be starting from the day your services are established and in advance of using such services. BADSHA HANDICAPPERS reserves the right to change the subscription terms and fees as per the racing schedule. Support if your service includes access to priority email support. “Email support” means the ability to make requests for technical support assistance by email at any time (with reasonable efforts by Badsha Handicapper to respond within three business day) concerning the use of the Services. All support will be provided in accordance with Badsha Handicapper standard services practices, procedures and policies.\n\n


2. Payment Terms.\nBy selecting a product or service, you agree to pay Badsha Handicapper the daily, weekly and/or monthly subscription fees indicated (additional payment terms if any may be included in other communications). Subscription payments will be charged on a pre-pay basis on the day you sign up for and will cover the use of that service for a subscription period as indicated. Payments are not refundable\n\n


3. Responsibility of Mobile App End User\nBadsha Handicapper has not reviewed, and cannot review, all of the material, including computer software, posted to the Mobile App, and cannot therefore be responsible for that material’s content, use or effects. By operating the Mobile App, Badsha Handicapper does not represent or imply that it endorses the material there posted, or that it believes such material to be accurate, useful or non-harmful. You are responsible for taking precautions as necessary to protect yourself and your computer systems, Mobile phone, Tab etc. from viruses, worms, Trojan horses, and other harmful or destructive content. The Mobile app may contain content that is offensive, or otherwise objectionable, as well as content containing technical inaccuracies, typographical mistakes, and other errors. The Mobile app may also contain material that violates the privacy or publicity rights, or infringes the intellectual property and other proprietary rights, of third parties, or the downloading, copying or use of which is subject to additional terms and conditions, stated or unstated. Badsha Handicapper disclaims any responsibility for any harm resulting from the use by end user of the Mobile App, or from any downloading by those visitors of content there posted.\n\n


4. Content of Other Websites\nWe have not reviewed, and cannot review, all of the material, including computer software, made available through the websites and web pages to which Badsha Handicapper links, and that link to Badsha Handicapper, Badsha Handicapper does not have any control over those non-Badsha Handicapper websites and webpages, and is not responsible for their contents or their use. By linking to a non-Badsha Handicapper mobile app, website or webpage, Badsha Handicapper does not represent or imply that it endorses such mobile app, website or webpage. You are responsible for taking precautions as necessary to protect yourself and your computer systems, Mobile Phone and Tab etc. from viruses, worms, Trojan horses, and other harmful or destructive content. Badsha Handicapper disclaims any responsibility for any harm resulting from your use of non-Badsha Handicapper mobile app, websites and Webpages.\n\n


5. Copyright Infringement and DMCA Policy\nAs Badsha Handicapper asks others to respect its intellectual property rights, it respects the intellectual property rights of others. If you believe that material located on or linked to by Badsha Handicapper violates your copyright, you are encouraged to notify Badsha Handicapper in accordance with Badsha Handicapper’s Digital Millennium Copyright Act (“DMCA”) Policy. Badsha Handicapper will respond to all such notices, including as required or appropriate by removing the infringing material or disabling all links to the infringing material. Badsha Handicapper will terminate a visitor’s access to and use of the Mobile app if, under appropriate circumstances, the visitor is determined to be a repeat infringer of the copyrights or other intellectual property rights of Badsha Handicapper or others. In the case of such termination, Badsha Handicapper will have no obligation to provide a refund of any amounts previously paid to Badsha Handicapper.\n\n


6. Intellectual Property\nThis Agreement does not transfer from Badsha Handicapper to you any Badsha Handicapper or third party intellectual property, and all right, title and interest in and to such property will remain (as between the parties) solely with Badsha Handicapper. Badsha Handicapper, Badsha Handicapper.com, the Badsha Handicapper.com logo, and all other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with Badsha Handicapper.com, or the Website are trademarks or registered trademarks of Badsha Handicapper or Badsha Handicapper’s licensors. Other trademarks, service marks, graphics and logos used in connection with the Website may be the trademarks of other third parties. Your use of the Website grants you no right or license to reproduce or otherwise use any Badsha Handicapper or third-party trademarks.\n\n


7. Advertisements\nBadsha Handicapper reserves the right to display advertisements on your screen.\n\n


8. Attribution\nBadsha Handicapper reserves the right to display attribution links such as ‘Blog at Badsha Handicapper.com,’ theme author, and font attribution in your blog footer or toolbar.\n\n


9. Modification\nBadsha Handicapper reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace any part of this Agreement. It is your responsibility to check this Agreement periodically for changes. Your continued use of or access to the mobile app BADSHA HANDICAPPER following the posting of any changes to this Agreement constitutes acceptance of those changes. Badsha Handicapper may also, in the future, offer new services and/or features through the Mobile App Such new features and/or services shall be subject to the terms and conditions of this Agreement.\n\n


10. Discontinuation and Termination of Services\nBadsha Handicapper may discontinue your access to all or any part of the Mobile App at any time, with or without cause, with or without notice, effective immediately. If you wish to discontinue this Agreement or your Badsha Handicapper account (if you have one), you may simply discontinue using it or uninstall the Mobile App from your Mobile Instrument. Notwithstanding the foregoing, if you have a paid services account, such account can only be terminated by Badsha Handicapper if you materially breach this Agreement and fail to cure such breach within Seven (7) days from Badsha Handicapper’s notice to you thereof; provided that, Badsha Handicapper can terminate the Mobile App immediately as part of a general shut down of our service. All provisions of this Agreement which by their nature shall survive termination, including, without limitation, ownership provisions, warranty disclaimers, indemnity and limitations of liability.\n\n


11. Disclaimer Warranty\nIn no event will Badsha Handicapper, or its Developer or licensors, be liable with respect to any subject matter of this agreement under any contract, negligence, strict liability or other legal theory for (1) any incidental or consequential damages (2) The cost of procurement for substitute products or services (3) for interruption of use or loss or corruption of data and (4) for any amounts that exceed the fees paid by you to Badsha Handicapper under this agreement during the Subscription Period prior to the cause of action. Badsha Handicapper shall have no liability for any failure or delay due to matters beyond their reasonable control. The foregoing shall not apply to the extent prohibited by applicable law.\n\n


12. Liability\nIn no event will Badsha Handicapper, or its suppliers or licensors, be liable with respect to any subject matter of this agreement under any contract, negligence, strict liability or other legal or equitable theory for: (i) any special, incidental or consequential damages; (ii) the cost of procurement for substitute products or services; (iii) for interruption of use or loss or corruption of data; or (iv) for any amounts that exceed the fees paid by you to Badsha Handicapper under this agreement during the 12 month period prior to the cause of action. Badsha Handicapper shall have no liability for any failure or delay due to matters beyond their reasonable control. The foregoing shall not apply to the extent prohibited by applicable law.\n\n


13. General Representation and Warranty\nYou represent and warrant that (1) your use of the Mobile App will be in strict accordance with the Badsha Handicapper Privacy Policy, with this Agreement and with all applicable laws and regulations including without limitation any local laws or regulations in your country, state, city, or other governmental area, regarding online conduct and acceptable content, and including all applicable laws regarding the transmission of technical data in the country in which you reside and (2) your use of the Mobile app will not infringe or misappropriate the intellectual property rights of any third party.\n\n


14. Indemnification\nYou agree to indemnify and hold harmless Badsha Handicapper, its contractors, and its licensors, and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against any and all claims and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising out of your use of our mobile app Badsha Handicapper, including any information received via this mobile App not limited to your violation of this Agreement.\n\n


15. Non Transferable\nThat the account created by you on Badsha Handicapper and any amount paid to Badsha Handicapper or lying in account is non-transferable.\n\n


16. Miscellaneous\nThis Agreement constitutes the entire agreement between Badsha Handicapper and you concerning the subject matter hereof, and they may only be modified by a written amendment signed by an authorized executive of Badsha Handicapper, or by the posting by Badsha Handicapper of a revised version. Except to the extent applicable law, if any, provides otherwise, this Agreement any access to or use of the Mobile App will be governed by the applicable laws in India. Any dispute arising under this Agreement shall be referred to the sole arbitrator to be decided by both the parties mutually under the provisions of Arbitration and Conciliation Act, 1996 and the venue of such arbitration shall be at Hyderabad only. The language shall be English. If any part of this Agreement is held invalid or unenforceable, that part will be construed to reflect the parties’ original intent, and the remaining portions will remain in full force and effect. A waiver by either party of any term or condition of this Agreement or any breach thereof, in any one instance, will not waive such term or condition or any subsequent breach thereof. You may assign your rights under this Agreement to any party that consents to, and agrees to be bound by, its terms and conditions Badsha Handicapper may assign its rights under this Agreement without condition. This Agreement will be binding upon and will inure to the benefit of the parties, their successors and permitted assign.\n\n


Disclaimer\nThe information and materials contained or referred to on this Mobile App BADSHA PROFESSIONAL HANDICAPPER are for reference only.\nBadsha Handicapper makes no representation or warranty of any kind, express, implied or statutory, regarding material on this Mobile App services or the materials and information contained or referred to on each page associated with this App.\nThe information and materials contained on this App are subject to change without notice, are provided for general information only and should not be used as a basis for making any type of decisions.\nAny information received via this app may be verified after consulting primary or more information or after getting more specific and professional advice elsewhere We are only a service provider and information seller, tips/guidance sellers online and off line and we never take any kind of bets on us or on behalf of any one hence we are not liable nor will be held liable for your wagering you make elsewhere using our tips/advise.\nWe advise you to make your bets always with official race club terminals and bookies associated with race clubs only. We do not directly or indirectly represent your wager or any of our associates do not involve in any of your betting nature at any point of time whether past, present or future The tips are the personal judgment of the Badsha Handicapper Team engaged for this purpose and any of our rules and regulations do not bind you to follow or we do not make guarantee any return in a specified period of time.\nPlease note that you are in a speculative game and we are predicting the chances that may or may not come true The result of loss/profit of money or wealth or life is immaterial to our Badsha Handicapper mobile App Services and does not deserve reference on this speculative nature of game which Badsha Handicapper cannot and will not have any control on the outcome of races or events tipped by this App. A paid membership is not a guarantee to a winning selection at any given time and the phrases used to describe bet category in our tips or message prior to race start are not the legal terminology associated with race results after as the nature of game has and will have no control any time in future by the tipster.\nAny spam message sent to web admin by mobile SMS or mail will attract a penalty of imposing a penalty on our paid members ranging from permanently banning for use of services on the severity of violation. The period also includes denial access to our any pages as decided by the admin and access our content/services to your system or mobile or any gadget may/will be blocked using the available technology by the service provider/company/website.\nAvailability of Tips Service is subject to availability of Badsha Handicapper staff and in the event of illness, absenteeism ,leave of professionals engaged the management cannot be held responsible for the same and not liable for any compensation or damage Technical snags, server outage are beyond the control of management and every viewer of our online content or member is obliged to be aware of this class and things will be made good in the event of such eventuality in the reasonable period of time You are recommended to obtain such professional advice where appropriate at your own will, source and cost.\nAnd Badsha Handicapper accepts no liability and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly including special, incidental or consequential loss or damage from your use of this mobile App Services, howsoever arising, including any loss, damage or expense arising from, but not limited to, any defect, error, imperfection, fault, omission, mistake or inaccuracy on this web site, its contents or associated services, or due to any unavailability of the mobile App service or any part thereof or any contents or associated services.\nAny “off-site” web pages or hypertext link from this Mobile App exist for information purposes and are for your convenience only and BADSHA HANDICAPPER accepts no liability for any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly including special, indirect or consequential loss or damage from the accuracy or otherwise of materials or information contained on the pages of such linked sites.\nBadsha Handicapper’s inclusion of hyperlinks or “off-site” web pages does not imply any endorsement of the materials on such sites. All disputes are subject to the jurisdiction of Hyderabad Only.\nCopyright notice all contents, design and materials on this Mobile App (BADSHA HANDICAPPER) are protected by copyright laws. You may not change, reproduce, distribute, publicly perform, and publicly display this material in any way, unless authorized by Badsha Handicapper or the respective owner’s copyright.\nBADSHA HANDICAPPER take due care to publish accurate information however it is not responsible for any inaccuracy.\n\n

NOTE: Videos are not our properties they are the properties of respective clubs. We give only links available in free public domain for educative purpose and are not included in subscription.\n\nFor any technical support you can Email us at: badshahandicapper@gmail.com\n\n</string>


    <string name="RaceCard"><u>Race Card</u></string>
    <string name="check_internet">Please check internet connection</string>
    <string name="ScaleRating"><u>Scale Rating</u></string>
    <string name="SpeedRating"><u>Speed Rating</u></string>
    <string name="BendPositionRating"><u>Bend Position Rating</u></string>
    <string name="BestTips"><u>Day Best Horse</u></string>
    <string name="BestTips1">Good Bets</string>
    <string name="BestTips2">Day Best Horse</string>
    <string name="BADSHAHANDICAPPERCHOICES"><u>BADSHA HANDICAPPER CHOICES</u></string>
    <string name="BADSHAHANDICAPPERCHOICES1"><u>BADSHA HANDICAPPER CHOICES</u></string>
    <string name="Results"><u>Results</u></string>
    <string name="Eatingbets"><u>Eating Bets</u></string>
    <string name="Videos">VIDEOS</string>
    <string name="message"><b>Thank you for downloading</b>
Badsha Handicapper Tips Application. Our services will resume on 13-11-2020.</string>


    <string name="card_number">Card Number</string>
    <string name="mm_yy">MM/yy</string>
    <string name="card_holders_name">Name</string>
    <string name="cvv">CVV</string>
    <string name="proceed">Proceed with Card</string>
    <string name="example_name">Test Name</string>
    <string name="example_email">android-sdk-sample-app@instamojo.com</string>
    <string name="example_phone">9876543210</string>
    <string name="example_amount">10</string>
    <string name="test_description">Test description</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="loader_message">Please wait&#8230;</string>
    <string name="naboutus"><u>BADSHA PROFESSIONAL HANDICAPPER</u>\n\nBadsha has been one of the most trusted names in Horse Racing and tipping for over a decade.\nHe has a simple rule.\nThe punter must go home with more than he entered the betting ring.\nWith this philosophy, he has managed to make thousands of punters richer with his accurate race analysis and handicapping.\nHe now comes out with the mobile app to make the same advice available to the national audience.\nThe application is managed by Badsha and his committed and highly professional team who uses the best scientific tools to come out with the best choice of horse to bet on for win, place, SHP, THP and jackpot.\nThe complete process is overseen and managed by Badsha personally and the Speed Rating Algorithm is managed by Amitabh Dutta.\nThe app has been developed by<b> M90 Technologies</b>, Aurangabad under the strict supervision of Badsha.\nAll information and data provided herein this mobile App BADSHA PROFESSIONAL HANDICAPPER is for reference purpose only.\nBADSHA HANDICAPPER make no representation or warranty of any kind regarding data on this Mobile App Services nor the data and information published or referred to on each pages associated with this App.\nAlso note videos are the properties of the respective clubs.\nBADSHA only gives a link to the respective race club’s websites or to the one which are available in public domain.\nVideos will play only if they are in compatible form.\nBADSHA Tips subscription doesnt includes Videos.\nThe Videos and its availability is not guaranteed by us.\nCONTACT:\nEMAIL: badshahandicapper@gmail.com\nWHAT DO YOU GET WITH THE DIAMOND PLAN\n\n1) RACE CARD: Day card details with last run details and the video of the last run if available.\n\n2) TRACKWORK: Track work of the horse after his last run till the date of the race.\n\n3) BADSHA HANDICAPPER CHOICE: Race wise choice of BADSHA including WIN, SHP, THP.TANALA, JACKPOT PICKS.\n\n4) BEST BETS: This page will offer Days Best, Good Double, Good Place, Lay bet, Treble and Jackpot.\n\n5) MEDIA TIPS: The tips from all major media outlets covering racing including the major blog sites.\n\n6)SCALE RATING The difference between the top weight horse and the bottom weight horse is called the scale and has a huge significance on how to read the race card. For instance, if the scale of the race is very wide with the top weight at 62 kgs and bottom weight at 45 kgs, the horses carrying the flyweight on their backs have a higher chance of winning even if they are not as prodigious as the top weight horses. If the scale is small, then the weight differential is lesser and only applies to the line through which the horses have run together in the past. In short, scale analysis helps you decipher the effect of the weight the horse is carrying. We will help you take informed decision with regards to the chances that a horse has based on the weight it s carrying.\n\n7) SPEED RATING Most punters are confused on how to compare two horses which have run at different weights under different conditions with different jockeys because all these factors affect the final position of the horse. Thus a horse carrying 60 kgs will travel slower than a horse traveling at 55 kgs. It’s easier to run on hard ground than soft ground. So how can you compare two horses? With our proprietary algorithm, we put values for all these variables, factoring in weight, jockeys and trainers abilities, and condition of the ground, wind speed, length of the straight, and distance from the rails etc. to arrive at a figure that you can use to easily compare two horses. This figure can help you select between all the possible horses and make an efficient decision on your betting.\n\n8) BEND POSITION ANALYSIS The bend position is a major contributor to the ability of the horse in winning a race. When we analyse the chances of a horse winning a race, we have to look at the aerodynamics of horse racing. Horses which hit the bend early find it easier to navigate the turn unless a backmarker can get an opening through the bunch ahead. On the other hand, in order to hit the bend early, the horse has to expend more energy making it vulnerable in the straight if it cannot get the necessary wind to overhaul the final stages. Therefore most long distance races, the clever jockey will position his horse in the pace so that it does not have to face the air resistance when turning 3 or 4 deep. We will help you understand when the horse is probable to hit the bend and how does that affect its chances in the race.\n\n9) RESULT: The result will be displayed only after being officially announced by the club’s website or announced at race course board.\n\nGuidelines\nWIN: The Horse should finish FIRST.\n\nSECOND HORSE POOL (SHP): The Horse should finish SECOND.\n\nTHIRD HORSE POOL (THP): The Horse should finish THIRD.\n\nPLACE: The Horse should finish in FIRST TWO. (If 7 runner)\n\nThe Horse should finish in FIRST THREE. (If above 7 runner)\n\nTANALA: The Horse should finish 1-2-3 or 2-3-1 or 3-2-1. (Any order from 1 to 3)\n\nJACKPOT: Select WINNER Horse of nominated 5 Races by club.\n\nWe will provide you with the best selections for the Jackpot ticket and the price of the same.\n\n</string>

    <!--<string name="base_url">http://badsha.cricketnewshub.xyz/public/api/</string>-->
    <string name="base_url">http://badsha.avistore.in/public/api/</string>
    <string name="something_went_wrong">Something Went Wrong</string>


</resources>